在这个时代，我们都有数以万计的图像存储在我们的计算机中。
We all have tens of thousands of images stored in our computer in this day and age.
这是我个人收藏的一些图片，也就是我度假的图片
Here’re some images from my own personal collection, the ones that I took on a holiday
几年前到澳大利亚北部。有睡莲，鸟类的照片，
to the northern part of Australia a few years ago. There are pictures of water lilies, birds,
树木，日落，原住民的岩石艺术和鳄鱼。此集合中的每个图像都存储在
trees, sunsets, Aboriginal rock art, and crocodiles. Every image in this collection is stored in
我计算机文件系统中的单个文件。让我们选择这条特别的鳄鱼
an individual file in the file system of my computer. Let’s select this particular crocodile
图像在这里，我们可以看到它所在的文件。这是一台Mac，所以我来到这里和我
image here and we can see which file it is in. This is a Mac, so I come up here and I
将在Mac的文件浏览器实用程序Finder中查看该文件。在Linux下，
will look at the file in the Mac’s file browser utility called Finder. Under Linux,
Windows，有相应的应用程序。在这里我们可以看到特定的文件
Windows, there are equivalent applications. And here we can see the particular file that
认为鳄鱼形象。我们可以看到它有一个.JPG扩展名，这意味着它
holds that crocodile image. We can see that it has a .JPG extension, that means it is
一个JPEG图像，我们将很快讨论这意味着什么，我们可以看到它是3.7
a JPEG image and we will talk about what that means shortly, and we can see that it is 3.7
兆字节长。现在我们可以在常规中打开该图像
megabytes long. Now we can open that image in the regular
Mac上的图像浏览器，在这种情况下，它是名为Preview的应用程序。那里
image browser on the Mac, and in this case it is the application called Preview. There
我们看到鳄鱼在屏幕上隐约可见。我们可以放大这个图像和
we see the crocodile looming large on the screen. And we can zoom into this image and
当我们放大时，我们看到图像变得越来越像块状。当我们向右缩放时
as we zoom in we see that the image becomes more and more block-like. And as we zoom right
我们可以看到图像是由这些微小的块组成的。这些是最小的
in we can see that the image is made up of these tiny little blocks. These are the smallest
图片中的元素。我们称它们为像素，这是像素的缩写。
elements within the picture. We call them pixels, that’s short for picture elements.
所以你在这里看到的是构成这个特定图像的单个像素。
So what you are seeing here are individual pixels that comprise this particular image.
让我们回到原来的位置。对于每个特定的图像，以及
Let’s go back to where we were. For each particular image, as well as the
包含图像本身的数据，构成图像的像素，有
data that comprises the image itself, the pixels that make up the picture, there is
一堆称为元数据的附加信息。我们可以看看
a bunch of additional information which is referred to as metadata. And we can look at
此处单击此按钮可以显示此图像的元数据。现在，显示元数据
the metadata for this image by clicking this button here. Now, the metadata is displayed
在顶角，有相当多的。首先，我们可以看到模型
up in the top corner, and there is quite a bit of it. First of all, we can see the model
拍摄这些照片的相机号码。我们可以看到图像的分辨率和
number of the camera that took these pictures. We can see the resolution of the image and
也就是说，图像宽3248像素，高2160像素。我们可以看到图像
that is that the image is 3248 pixels wide by 2160 pixels tall. We can see that the image
磁盘上的长度为3.7兆字节。我们可以看到焦距或缩放设置
is 3.7 megabytes long on the disk. We can see the focal length or the zoom setting that
当我拍摄这张特别的照片时我用过。我可以看到F-stop或光圈设置。
I used when I took this particular picture. I can see the F-stop or aperture setting.
我还可以看到拍摄这张特殊照片时的曝光时间或快门时间。
And I can also see the exposure time or shutter time when I took this particular picture.
更现代的相机会有额外的元数据，例如GPS坐标
More modern cameras would have additional metadata, for things like the GPS coordinate
拍摄图像的地方有许多不同类型的图像
of the place where the image was captured. There are many, many different types of image
今天常用的格式。如果你去看维基百科，你可以在那里找到
format commonly used today. If you go and look on Wikipedia, you can find that there
有数百种不同类型的图像文件格式。我在这里列出了一些
are hundreds of different types of image file format. I have listed here just a few of the
最常见的。JPEG是格式文件，通常具有.jpg或的文件扩展名
most common ones. JPEG are format files which typically have a file extension of .jpg or
.JPEG。TIFF文件，GIF文件，便携式网络图形或PNG文件等等。什么时候
.jpeg. TIFF files, GIF files, Portable network graphics or PNG files, and many others. When
我们实际上看一个图像文件，它有三个独立的组件，并且
we actually look inside an image file, it has really three separate components, and
他们生活在我们称之为容器的地方。所以我们这里有一个空容器。一个
they live within what we call a container. So here we have an empty container. And one
容器中的第一个元素是所谓的标题和标题
of the first elements in the container is what is called the header, and the header
包含有关图像有多大，图像有多宽，有多高和有多高的信息
contains information about how big the image is, how wide it is, how tall it is and the
压缩类型和像素格式的类型。是每像素8位，10位
type of compression, and the type of pixel format. Is it eight bits per pixel, ten bits
每像素或其他什么。容器中的下一个对象是什么
per pixel or whatever. The next object in the container is what is
称为元数据，其中包含有关拍摄的实际图片的信息。它
called the metadata, and that has information about the actual picture that was taken. It
拍摄照片时可能具有相机的GPS坐标。它可能有
might have the GPS coordinate of the camera when the picture was taken. It might have
F数和焦距，以及闪光是否发射。所以这是信息
the F number and the focal length, and whether the flash fired or not. So it is information
关于拍摄的特定照片。然后，最后我们有了实际的像素
about that particular picture that was taken. And then, finally we have the actual pixel
数据本身，代表图像的信息，它可以被压缩或不被压缩
data itself, the information which represents the image and it may be compressed or not
压缩。所以当我们谈论图像文件格式时，我们
compressed. So when we talk about image file format, we
需要实际谈论两件事。我们需要谈谈特定的容器
need to actually talk about two things. We need to talk about the particular container
保存此信息并且有不同类型的容器。我们也是
that holds this information and there are different types of containers. And we also
需要讨论应用于图像像素的不同压缩方法
need to talk about the different compression methods which are applied to the image pixel
数据。所以当我们通常谈论JPEG文件时，
data. So when we commonly talk about a JPEG file,
JPEG格式文件，正确的我们应该说这是一个EXIF容器
JPEG format file, correctly we should be saying that this is an EXIF container that holds
JPEG压缩图像数据。
JPEG compressed image data.